Robert S. McNamara Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Organizations, 1969-2006 (Box II:5-36)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States, 1994-2005
  - Battelle Memorial Institute
    - General, 1995-1998
    - Global Climate Change and the Social Sciences project, 1993-1994
    - Human Choice and Climate Change, 1995-1998
    - Meetings
      - “History of the 21st Century,” Cosmos Club, Washington, D.C., 2000
      - International Advisory Board (Box II: 9)
        - London, England, 1995
        - Periodic meetings, 1995-1997
  - Brookings Institution
    - Board of Trustees
      - Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1996
      - Profiles, 1993-1995
    - General
      - 1982-1990, (3 folders)
      - 1991-2005, (2 folders) (Box II: 10)
    - Reports, 2003-2004
    - “Values” seminars, 1989-1991
  - California Institute of Technology, Pasadena, Calif., 1997-2005
  - Carnegie Corp. of New York
    - Carnegie Commission on Preventing Deadly Conflict
      - Briefing book, 1995
      - General, 1994-1996, (2 folders) (Box II: 11)
    - General, 1991, 1997-1998
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
    - Commission on the Role of the MDBs in Emerging Markets, 2001
    - International Crisis Group
      - General, 1994-1995
      - London Conference, London, England, 1994-1995
    - Non-Proliferation Conference, Washington, D.C., 2005
    - U.S.-Japan Study Group on Arms Control and Non-Proliferation After the Cold War
      - General, 1994-1995
      - Meeting, Tokyo, Japan, 1995 (Box II: 12)
        - Background book
        - General
  - Center for Global Development, 2003-2005
  - Committee on Agricultural Sustainability for Developing Countries, 1993-1995
  - Comprehensive Objective Research on Proposed Solutions, 1997
  - Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research, 1979, 1993-2005
  - Corning Incorporated
    - General, 1985-2005, (3 folders)
    - Investment Advisory Committee, meetings, 1996-1998 (Box II: 13)
  - Council on Foreign Relations
    - Conferences and meetings
      - 1995, Nov. 6-15, “Missed Opportunities?” Hanoi, Vietnam, 1995-1996 See also Container II:73, same heading
      - 1998, Jan. 30, “Conference on Nigeria,” New York, N.Y., 1997-1998
    - General, 1995-2006, (2 folders)
    - Nominations for membership, 1985, 1992-1999
    - Working Group on the Elimination of Nuclear Weapons, 1996
  - Drug Strategies
    - “Attorney General's Report on Promising Strategies to Reduce Substance Abuse,” draft, 2000
    - Board of Directors, meetings, 1994-2001, (2 folders) (Box II: 14)
    - General, 1993-2005, (2 folders)
    - Press clippings, 1991-2001
  - Earth Council
    - 1993-1994
    - 1995-1999 (Box II: 15)
  - East African Development Bank
    - General, 1996-2006, (2 folders)
    - Meetings, 1998, 2003, (2 folders)
    - Reports
      - Annual, 1997-2005
      - Creditworthiness, 1996
      - Diagnostic and recommendations for reform, 2003 (Box II: 16)
      - Financial, 1997-2002
    - Robert McNamara/EADB Graduate Scholarship in Development Studies, 2004-2005
  - Economists Allied for Arms Reduction, 1994-1998
  - Eisenhower Seminar, 2000-2004
  - Eminent Persons Group on Curbing Illicit Trafficking in Small Arms and Light Weapons
    - Convocation, United Nations, New York, N.Y., 2001
    - General, 1996-2004 See also Classified, (3 folders)
    - Visit of Michel Rocard, briefing book, 2000 (Box II: 17)
  - Eminent Persons on Population and Development, meeting, Tokyo, Japan, 1993-1994, (2 folders)
  - Enterprise Foundation
    - General, 1996-2006, (3 folders)
    - Meetings
      - Board of Directors
        - 1994-1995
        - 1998, (2 folders) (Box II: 18)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1996-1997, (2 folders)
    - Sandtown-Winchester, Md., neighborhood transformation project, 1996
  - Environmental Development Consultants, 1993-1997
  - Ford Foundation, 1995-2004
  - Global Coalition for Africa
    - African Population Advisory Committee, 1997
    - “Africa's Development Crisis,” statement by McNamara, 1991
    - Conferences and meetings
      - 1991, Sept. 9-10, first Advisory Committee meeting, Paris, France
      - 1992, May 8-9, second Advisory Committee meeting, Kampala, Uganda (Box II: 19)
        - General, 1991-1992
        - Reports and papers, nos. 2-12, 1992, (2 folders)
        - Statements by McNamara, 1992
      - 1995
        - Sept. 4-5, cochairmens' meeting, Gaborone, Botswana
        - Nov. 23-28, “Africa's Future and the World,” Maastricht, Netherlands
      - 1996
        - Aug. 26-28, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia
          - Cochairpersons' meeting, 1995-1996
          - Economic Committee, 1996
        - Oct. 29-31, Policy Forum and Political Committee meetings, Ouagadougou, Burkina Faso (Box II: 20)
          - General
          - Notes
          - Reports and papers
      - 2000, June 28-29, chairpersons meeting, Geneva, Switzerland
      - 2003, Jan. 22-23, Policy Forum, Accra, Ghana, 2001-2003
    - General
      - 1990-1995, Feb., (2 folders)
      - 1995, Mar.-2005, (2 folders) (Box II: 21)
    - Reports and studies, 1992-1996
  - Harry S. Truman Fund for the Advancement of the Human Condition, 1992-1997
  - Henry L. Stimson Center
    - General, 1995-1999
    - Project on Eliminating Weapons of Mass Destruction, Steering Committee
      - 1993-1995, Oct., (2 folders)
      - 1995, Nov.-1998, (3 folders) (Box II: 22)
  - Honorary Presidential Advisory Council on Investment in Nigeria
    - Background material, 2000-2003
    - Conferences and meetings
      - 2001
        - Feb. 27-28, Abuja, Nigeria, 2000-2001
        - Sept. 24-25, Nigeria Investment Summit, London, England, 2000-2001, (2 folders)
      - 2002
        - Apr. 18-19, Abuja, Nigeria
          - Agenda and reports, 2002
          - General, 2000-2002 (Box II: 23)
        - July 16-17, London, England
      - 2003
        - Jan. 13-14, “Nigeria Going Forward,” Abuja, Nigeria
          - Background material, 2002-2003
          - General, 2002-2003
          - Reports and papers, 2003
        - Nov. 28-30, Abuja, Nigeria
          - Background material, 2003
          - General, 2003-2004
    - Correspondence, 2000-2004
    - Reports, 2001-2003 (Box II: 24)
  - Indira Gandhi Memorial Trust
    - Conferences
      - 1997, Nov. 19-22, “Post Colonial World Inter-dependence and Identities,” sixth conference, New Delhi, India, 1997-1998
      - 1999, Nov. 19-22, “New Century: Whose Century?” seventh conference, New Delhi, India
    - Indira Gandhi Prize, International Jury, 1994-2002, (4 folders)
  - Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation, 1996-1997
  - InterAction Council
    - Conferences and meetings, 2005
      - Mar. 30-Apr. 2, High-Level Expert Group meetings, Santa Clara University, Santa Clara, Calif.
        - General, 2004-2005
        - Reports and papers, 2005
      - June 22-23, twenty-third plenary meeting, Stanford University, Stanford, Calif.
      - June 23-25, World Leaders' Summit, sponsored by the Saga Foundation, Stanford University, Stanford, Calif., 2004-2005 (Box II: 25)
    - General, 1991-2005, (2 folders)
  - International Committee to Protect the World's Children, 1979-1983
  - International Food Policy Research Institute
    - Conference, “Assuring Food and Nutrition Security in Africa by 2020,” Kampala, Uganda, 2004
    - General, 1993-2001, (2 folders)
    - Press conference, remarks by McNamara, 1996 (Box II: 26)
  - International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1997-2000
  - Kettering Foundation
    - China-U.S. Dialogue meetings
      - 1995, Oct. 9-13, Beijing, China
        - Background book, 1995
        - General, 1994-1995
      - 2005, Sept. 27-29, Beijing, China
    - General, 1996, 2005
  - Lawyers Alliance for World Security
    - General, 1992-1993, 1998-2001
    - National defense consultations, 2001
  - Learning Wise, Inc., 2001-2005
  - Liu Centre for the Study of Global Issues, 1998-1999
  - Logistics Management Institute, 1993, 2000-2005
  - Miscellaneous, A-T, 1985, 1996-2006
  - National Committee on United States-China Relations
    - Board of Directors and Executive Committee
      - General, 1991-2005
      - Meetings
        - 1991-1999, (2 folders)
        - 2000-2005, (3 folders) (Box II: 27)
    - Conferences and meetings
      - 1994, May 22-June 4, “Security Issues Workshop,” Beijing, China
        - Background material, 1993-1994
        - General, 1994
        - Papers and speeches
          - By McNamara, 1994
          - By others, 1994
      - 1995, Nov. 30-Dec. 10, eighth U.S.-China Dialogue, Beijing, China
    - General, 1987-2005
  - National Institute for the Environment, 1995-2000 (Box II: 28)
  - Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development
    - Conference, “The Conversion of China's Military Industries,” Beijing, China, 1995
    - Correspondence, 1997
  - Overseas Development Council
    - Conferences and meetings, 1995-1998
    - General, 1982-2000, (2 folders)
  - Philadelphia Liberty Medal, International Selection Commission, 1989-2001
  - Population Action International, 1997-1998, 2005
  - Pugwash Conferences on Science and World Affairs (Box II: 29)
    - British Pugwash Group
      - Edinburgh International Science Festival, Edinburgh, Scotland, 1998
        - General, 1997-1998
        - Speeches and writings, 1998
          - By McNamara, “Reflections on War in the 21st Century”
          - By others
      - WMD Awareness Programme, 2005
    - General, 1986-2005
    - Workshops
      - 1991
        - May 3-4, “Desirability and Feasibility of a Nuclear-Weapon-Free World,” Turin, Italy
        - June 8-9, twentieth workshop on nuclear forces, Geneva, Switzerland
      - 1997, Feb. 7-9, twenty-sixth workshop on nuclear forces, Geneva, Switzerland, 1996-1997
      - 1999, Oct. 22, “Discussion on Intervention and Sovereignty,” Cambridge, Mass.
  - Rajiv Gandhi Foundation, 1989-1997
  - Reading Is Fundamental (Box II: 30)
    - Correspondence, 1981-2001, (2 folders)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1982-1984
    - Miscellany, 1981-1986, 1995-2001
  - Rockefeller Foundation, conferences and meetings
    - 1991, Dec. 3, organizational meeting for proposal of a commission on population, London, England, 1990-1992
    - 1994, Jan. 17-19, “Technology Transfer and Non-Proliferation,” National Institute of Advanced Studies, Bangalore, India
      - Background material, 1990-1994
      - General, 1993-1994
    - 1995, June 18-21, “Options for Indo-US Cooperation,” Pocantico Hills, N.Y.
      - Background material, 1994-1995
      - General, 1995
  - Save the Children, 1995 (Box II: 31)
  - Search for Common Ground, 2001-2006
  - Transparency International, 1992-2001, (3 folders)
  - Trilateral Commission
    - General
      - 1983-2004, Feb., (2 folders)
      - 2004, Mar.-2005 (Box II: 32)
    - Meetings
      - 1991, Oct. 18-20, fifteenth European regional meeting, Brussels, Belgium
        - General
        - Papers and speeches
          - By McNamara, “Security in the Post Cold-War World”
          - By others
      - 1997, Mar. 22-24, plenary meeting, Tokyo, Japan
    - Writings, 1991
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America, 1996, 2004-2005
  - United States-Japan Foundation
    - Board of Trustees, meetings, 1988-1998
    - General, 1981-1994, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1982-1987
  - Urban Institute
    - 1983-1987
    - 1988-2005, (4 folders) (Box II: 33)
  - Washington Council on Non-Proliferation, 1989-1992, (2 folders)
  - Washington Post, 1969, 1977 (Box II: 34)
  - World Commission on Water for the 21st Century, 1998-2000
  - World Food Prize Foundation
    - General, 1992-2005, (3 folders)
    - Meetings
      - 1996, Oct. 17-20, “Food Security: New Solutions for the 21st Century,” Des Moines, Iowa
        - Background book, 1996
        - General, 1995-1996, (2 folders)
        - Programs and invitations, 1996 (Box II: 35)
        - Speech by McNamara, drafts, 1996
      - 1997, Oct. 15-18, “Perspectives on Food Security in Africa,” Des Moines, Iowa
  - World Future Society, 1997-2005
  - World Resources Institute
    - 1982-1997, (5 folders)
    - 1998-1999 (Box II: 36)
  - Yosemite Restoration Trust, 1990-1996
- Part II: Subject File, 1946-2006 (Box II:36-77)
  Correspondence, memoranda, conferences and meetings, position papers, background briefings, reports and studies, drafts and typescripts, background material, briefing books, secretary of defense's daily calenders, notes, transcripts, statements and testimony, interviews, speeches and writings, press releases, printed matter, and miscellaneous material.
  - Agriculture, 1993-1996 (Box II:36)
  - Archives and personal papers
    - John F. Kennedy Library, Boston, Mass.
      - Correspondence, 1996-2005
      - Tape recordings
        - Correspondence, 1996-2005
        - Recording logs and transcripts, 1962-1963, 2003-2004
    - Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, Austin, Tex., 1985, 1993-1997, 2005
    - National Archives and Records Administration, 1992-1994
  - Arms control and nuclear weapons
    - Committee on Nuclear Policy, 1997-1998
    - Comprehensive Test Ban Treaty, 1999-2001
    - Correspondence, 1990-2005 (Box II: 37)
    - General, 1981, 1989-2005
    - Non-Proliferation Treaty, 2000-2005
    - Nuclear bombing of Japan, 1994-1995
    - Press clippings, 1981, 1988-2004
    - Printed matter, 1978-1981, 1988-2004, undated, (4 folders)
    - Reports, 1981, 1991-1994, 2003-2004, (2 folders) (Box II: 38)
    - Statements, 1993-2002
    - Summit Meeting, notes concerning, 1985
  - Automotive Hall of Fame, Dearborn, Mich., 1995-1997
  - Bay of Pigs invasion, fortieth anniversary, 1959-1961, 2000-2001
  - Commissions
    - Canberra Commission on the Elimination of Nuclear Weapons
      - Background material, 1996, undated, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1995
        - 1996 (Box II: 39)
      - General, 1995-1996, undated, (2 folders)
      - Media and press, 1996
      - Meetings, 1996
        - Jan. 23-25
          - Background papers, 1996
          - General, 1995-1996
        - Apr. 22-24 (Box II: 40)
          - Background papers
          - “Draft Elements of the Report”
          - General
        - July 13-15
        - Aug. 12-14
          - Background papers
          - General
      - Notes, 1996
      - Report, 1996
        - Drafts
          - Annex A, “Verification Arrangements”
          - First draft, corrected copy (Box II: 41)
          - Revised draft
        - Published report
    - Commission on Executive, Legislative, and Judicial Salaries, 1986-1991
    - National Commission on the Public Service, 1987-1989
    - President's Commission on White House Fellowships, 1992
    - Rivlin Commission, 1994, 2000
  - Conferences and meetings
    - 1993, May 24, Center for East-West Trade Policy, Richard B. Russell Symposium, University of Georgia, Athens, Ga.
    - 1994
      - July 22-24, “Change: Social Conflict or Harmony?” United Nations Development Programme, Stockholm, Sweden
      - Oct. 24-26, Tokyo Conference on Global Environmental Action, Tokyo, Japan
    - 1995 (Box II: 42)
      - Jan. 14, International Seminar on the Lessons of the Cuban Missile Crisis, Center for Policy Research, New Delhi, India, 1994-1995
      - Oct. 16-18, “Moving Africa into the 21st Century,” North South Roundtable, Johannesburg, South Africa
    - 1996, Oct. 24, “U.S. Environmental Priorities and Strategies in the New Independent States, Central and Eastern Europe, and China,” Woodrow Wilson Center, Washington, D.C.
    - 2003
      - Jan. 9, “Focus on Global Security,” Young President's Organization, San Francisco, Calif., 2002-2003
      - Sept. 29-Oct. 1, Third Tokyo International Conference on African Development, Tokyo, Japan, 2001-2003
    - 2004, May 12-13, “The World Today,” Universal Forum of Cultures, Barcelona, Spain
    - 2005, Dec. 14-15, “Nuclear and Non-Nuclear Forces in 21st-Century Deterrence,” Thirty-Sixth Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, Washington, D.C.
  - Congressional testimony, House Budget Committee, 1988-1991
  - Cuban Missile Crisis
    - Blight, James G., 1988-1995, (2 folders)
    - Chronologies, 1990 (Box II: 43)
    - Cuban Missile Crisis Project, conferences and meetings
      - 1987
        - Mar. 5-8, Hawk's Cay Conference, Marathon, Fla.
          - General, 1987
          - Proceedings, 1988
        - Oct. 11-12, Cambridge Conference, Cambridge, Mass.
          - Drafts of proceedings
            - Revised, 1987
            - Final, 1988
          - General, 1987
      - 1989, Jan. 27-28, Trilateral Symposium on the Caribbean Crisis (Moscow Conference), Moscow, Soviet Union
        - Drafts and notes, 1988-1989
        - General, 1982, 1988-1989
        - Proceedings, 1989 (Box II: 44)
      - 1991, Jan. 3-7, “Cuba between the Superpowers,” Antigua
        - Blight, James G., 1990-1991
        - Transcript and appendices, 1991
      - 1992, Jan. 9-12, Havana Conference, Havana, Cuba
        - Background material
          - Cuban economy, 1990
          - Cuban subversion, 1961-1963, 1972, 1990-1991
          - General, 1963, 1990-1992
        - Correspondence, 1991-1992
        - General, 1991-1992 (Box II: 45)
        - Notes, 1992
        - Opening statement, drafts, 1992
        - Press conference, 1992
      - 2002, Oct. 11-12, “The October Crisis: A Political Perspective Forty Years Later,” Havana Conference, Havana, Cuba
        - Correspondence, 2001-2003
        - Memorandum of conversation and notes, 2002
        - Miscellany, 1993, undated
        - Statements and writings by McNamara, 2001-2002
    - Exhibit for the John F. Kennedy Library, Boston, Mass., 1991
    - General, 1963, 1983-1984, 1992, 1998, 2004, undated
    - The Kennedy Tapes, edited by Ernest May and Phillip D. Zelikow, 1996-1998
    - Media, 1992, 1998 (Box II: 46)
    - Notes, 1992, 2005
    - Originals and copies of primary documents
      - Miscellany, 1962-1963, 1997 See also Classified
      - Transcription of tapes recorded in the cabinet room (Oct. 27, 1962), 1987
    - A Preliminary Catalogue of Documents, prepared by the National Security Archive, 1987
    - Soviet Views on the Cuban Missile Crisis, edited by Ronald R. Pope, 1982
    - Thirteen Days, motion picture, 1999-2001
    - Writings, 1991-1992
  - Defense department
    - Appointment as Secretary of Defense, letter of acceptance, 1960
    - Bay of Pigs operation, “Inspector General's Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (1962),” as released by the National Security Archive, 1997, (1 folder) (Box II: 47)
    - Briefings and statements, bound compilations
      - “Background Briefings of Secretary of Defense McNamara”
        - 1965
        - 1966 (Box II: 48)
      - “Public Statements of Secretary of Defense McNamara”
        - 1960-1961, Apr. 11
        - 1961, Apr. 13-Dec. 27, (2 vols.) (Box II: 49)
        - 1962 (Box II: 50)
          - Jan. 5-26
          - Jan. 29-Mar. 15 (Box II: 51)
          - Mar. 16-June 16 (Box II: 52)
        - 1963
          - Jan. 3-Feb. 4
          - Feb. 10-28 (Box II: 53)
        - 1964
          - Jan. 9-Feb. 5
          - Feb. 3-July 23, (2 vols.) (Box II: 54)
          - Aug. 5-Dec. 22 (Box II: 55)
        - 1965
          - Jan. 4-Feb. 18
          - Feb. 24-Mar. 5, (2 vols.) (Box II: 56)
          - June 16-Dec. 30 (Box II: 57)
        - 1966
          - Jan. 3-25
          - Jan. 26-Feb. 16, (2 vols.) (Box II: 58)
          - Feb. 23-Mar. 10, (2 vols.) (Box II: 59)
          - Mar. 11-Dec. 23, (2 vols.) (Box II: 60)
        - 1967 (Box II: 61)
          - Jan. 15-Mar. 1, (2 vols.)
          - Mar. 2-8, (2 vols.) (Box II: 62)
          - Mar. 6-Dec. 31, (2 vols.) (Box II: 63)
        - 1968, Jan.-May, (2 vols.) (Box II: 64)
  - Defense department (Box II: 65)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1963, 1975, 1993, 2001
    - Memoranda, position papers, and reports, 1961-1968 See also Classified, (3 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1961, 1968, 2006
    - National Reconnaissance Office, 1998-2000
    - Notification of personnel action, 1961, 1968, 1989
    - Nuclear Posture Review, 1993-1994, 2002 See also Classified
    - Papers of Robert S. McNamara, inventory lists, 1971
    - Reports and studies
      - Achievements and issues, 1968, undated See also Classified
      - “History of the Logistical Management Institute,” 1990 (Box II: 66)
    - Retirement, 1946, 1964-1969, 1980
    - Secretary's calendar (daily events, telephone calls, and visitors)
      - 1961-1962, (2 folders)
      - 1963-1964, (2 folders) (Box II: 67)
      - 1965-1967, (3 folders) (Box II: 68)
      - 1968 (Box II: 69)
    - Statement by McNamara before the Senate Armed Services Committee concerning the defense budget, 1968
    - Tonkin Gulf incident, declassified documents, 1964-1975, 2004
  - East-West relations, 1982-1984
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, Freedom of Information Act requests
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994
    - Investigative files, 1960-1976, 1997-1998, (2 folders)
    - Reports of threats, 1977-1978 (Box II: 70)
  - Ford Motor Co.
    - Corporate history project, interview, 1988-1992
    - Edsel automobile, 1969, 1976
    - General, 1946, 1960-1964, 1974, 1993-1998
  - Geopolitical file
    - Africa, 1990-1994
    - China, 1993-1994, 2005
    - India, 1991
    - Pakistan, 1992
  - Grameen Trust, Dhaka, Bangladesh, 1992-1995
  - International development (Box II: 71)
    - General, 1994, 2001
    - Microcredit
      - General, 1994-1996
      - Summit meetings, 1996-1997
    - Synergos Institute, 1993-1995
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., transcriptions of telephone conversations, 1963
  - Kennedy family
    - Assassination Records Review Board, 1996
    - General, 1968, 1993-2001
  - Onchocerciasis (river blindness) (Box II: 72)
    - Correspondence, 1991-2001
    - Miscellany, 1991-1994, 2000-2003
    - River Blindness Control Program
      - Meetings
        - Executive Directors, 1991-1992
        - Joint Action Forum, 1995, 2001, (2 folders)
        - Ministers, 1994
      - Report, 1990
      - Statue unveiling, 1997-1998
  - Restructuring American society, 1988, 1996-1997
  - Résumés and references, 1996-1998
  - Secretarial position, 1983-1984
  - Thomas J. Watson, Jr. Institute for International Studies, Brown University, Providence, R.I., 1991-1999 (Box II: 73)
  - Vietnam War Project: “Missed Opportunities?” See also Container II:80, Argument without End
    - Background material
      - Cold War International History Project, Woodrow Wilson Center, working papers, 1993-1998
      - Miscellaneous, 1964, 1993-1996, (2 folders)
      - Vietnamese biographies, 1980-1993
    - Conferences and meetings
      - 1995, Nov. 6-15, exploratory trip to Hanoi, Vietnam See also Container II:13, same heading
      - 1996 (Box II: 74)
        - Sept. 13, Cambridge, Mass.
        - Sept. 22, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y.
        - Dec. 3, Cambridge, Mass.
      - 1997
        - Jan. 20-21, Cambridge, Mass.
        - Apr. 4-6, Washington, D.C.
        - June 20-23, “Missed Opportunities?” Hanoi, Vietnam
          - Briefing book
          - General
          - Press coverage (Box II: 75)
          - Report notebook
          - Transcript of proceedings
      - 1998, Feb. 23-26, Hanoi, Vietnam, transcript of proceedings
      - 1999, “’Pennsylvania' to Paris” conferences
        - June 7-9, Hanoi, Vietnam
          - Background material
            - Briefing book
            - Discussion paper
            - Harriman, W. Averell, personal papers (declassified), 1967-1968
            - Transcribed notes of president's meetings (declassified), 1967-1968, (2 folders) (Box II: 76)
          - Correspondence
          - Transcript of proceedings
        - Dec. 9-12, White Oak Conference, Yulee, Fla.
          - Briefing book
          - General
    - Correspondence (Box II: 77)
      - Blight, James G., and Janet M. Lang
        - 1995-1997, (5 folders)
        - 1998-1999 (Box II: 78)